what's up my kids I'm being totally
qué pasa mi chavalería yo soy totalmente
honest today's video wasn't going to be about
sincero el vídeo de hoy no iba a tratar
what I'm going to be about as such but I had
de lo que voy a tratar como tal sino que
found an interview with one
había encontrado una entrevista de uno
of the members of our
de los componentes de nuestros
favorite scammers team 2 you watch
estafadores favoritos el team 2 tu ver
an interview on television I
en la televisión una entrevista
swear it's priceless okay and
os juro que no tiene desperdicio vale y
we're going to get a lot of laughs from there if you
vamos a sacar muchas risas de ahí si
want the next video to be that
queréis que el próximo vídeo sea esa
interview this television interview
entrevista esta entrevista en televisión
of this character how about this video
de este personaje qué tal este vídeo al
aik I'm just saying it's worth it what
aik sólo digo que merece la pena lo que
happens is that when recording that video I was going to
pasa que al grabar ese vídeo iba a
use as an intro a couple of clarifications
utilizar como intro par de aclaraciones
about a video that they uploaded
sobre un vídeo que han subido
acknowledging in quotes okay
reconociendo entre comillas vales
acknowledging that they have done something wrong
reconociendo que han hecho algo mal
regarding Kenya or now we're going to get to that
respecto a kenia o que ahora vamos a eso
but I was hooking up with Meliá Meliá
pero me ligaba meliá meliá meliá me he
Meliá I told myself that this is not for an intro this is worth a [ __ ] video and put these two scoundrels in their place are you really going to forgive me for the attitude of I'm going to have this video for me is to find and cross paths somewhere
encontrarme y cruzar me en algún lado
with these two that the word
con estos dos que es que la palabra
scoundrel describes them  perfectly
sinvergüenza los describe perfectamente
but I think they fall short and
pero yo creo que se les queda corto y
mayer my blood I swear my
mayer me la sangre lo juro que me hierve
blood boils because I said disgusting it turns out
la sangre que es que dije asco resultase
that they have uploaded some kind of questions
que han subido una especie de preguntas
and answers to their channel in which they
y respuestas a su canal en el cual
respond well they take the opportunity to clarify
responde bueno aprovechan para aclarar
everything that has supposedly happened with
todo lo que ha pasado supuestamente con
Kenya but it is that it does not clarify a
kenia pero es que no aclara en una
[ __ ], I mean they justify what they have done
mierda o sea justifican lo que han hecho
as a
como un
social experiment as a
experimento social como un experimento
social experiment I already thought that that was an
social yo ya pensaba que eso era una
excuse that had become a meme
excusa que se había convertido en meme
every time someone did something wrong that they
cada vez que alguien hacía una cagada
had no way of solving it was called the
que no tenía cómo resolverla se decía el
social experiment and nobody took it
experimento social y nadie lo tomaba en
seriously nobody justified that seriously it is
serio nadie se justificaba eso en serio
taken as a meme but the thing is that everyone
se toma como un meme pero es que todos
is a personified meme and they
son un meme personificado y quieren
still want or think that they can still fool
todavía o cree que todavía puede engañar
someone I just do not understand let's
a alguien es que no lo entiendo vamos a
watch this video prepare the kringe
ver este vídeo preparar el kringe
prepare the cricket because it is too much
preparar el cricket porque es demasiado
and it is going to boil your blood a lot but it
y os va a hervir mucho la sangre pero
could be the question that many of you have been
puede ser la pregunta que muchos estáis
waiting for since October 100 began
esperando desde que empezó el 100 de
and it is that I wanted to have never been
octubre y es que quería nunca ha formado
part of October 100 being I had an
parte del 100 de octubre siendo tuve una
idea that we have had
idea que hemos tenido nosotros
host what a surprise that she does not  is
hostia qué sorpresa que ella no forma
part of the October team and I that
parte del team de octubre y yo que
you two head in use and
ustedes dos cabezal en el uso y cabeza
pineapple head I saw you at the same level as me
de piña os veía al mismo nivel que yo
kilos or rather with the difference that your
kilos o sea con la diferencia de que sus
kilos are millionaire guys with 15
kilos son tíos millonarios con 15
million subscribers and lined with
millones de suscriptores y forrados en
cash and you are two unfortunate
billete y ustedes soy dos desgraciados
scammers from the village of Hello
estafadores de la aldea de la hello
Kitty who do not know how to vocalize well
kitty que no sabéis de vocalizar bueno
gosh who blames someone for not
vaya tela el que culpa a alguien de no
knowing how to vocalize not for the one who has
sabe vocalizar no para el que haya
lived in Narnia during this time or
vivido en narnia durante este tiempo o
six new subscribers on my channel
seis nuevos suscriptores en mi canal
these two have done the most filthy the most
estos dos han hecho lo más cerdo lo más
filthy thing that has been done on YouTube in all of
cerdo que se ha hecho en youtube en toda
history okay I'm going to leave you in the
la historia vale os voy a dejar en la
description the playlist and the
descripción la lista de reproducción y
most notable videos where they dismantled
los vídeos más destacable donde desmontó
these pair of scoundrels and
a este par de sinvergüenzas y descubra
everyone discovers what they have done so that you
todo el mundo lo que han hecho para que
find out in detail okay
os enteréis con pelos y señales vale
so that you don't miss any of the
para que no os perdáis ninguno de los
details and the blood will be very useful
detalles y os va a servir muchísimo la
but in short these two are two
sangre pero en resumen estos dos son dos
characters who have a salty channel
personajes que tienen un canal de sal se
and that it was not going well for them okay this
o y que no les iba nada bien vale este
this channel is not growing by three
este canal no creciente a la de tres
because they were  some slobs were
porque eran unos guarros eran unos
slobs and now we're going to see step by
guarro y ahora vamos a ir viendo paso a
step some of the things they did
paso algunas de las cosas que hicieron
they did very dirty things like
hacían cosas muy cerda como
uploading a video that only lasted
subiendo un vídeo que simplemente duraba
half a second with a green screen as a
medio segundo con una pantalla en verde
title to see this video you
que ponía de título para ver este vídeo
have to be subscribed to this channel or
tiene que estar suscrito a este canal o
for example making montages with the face
por ejemplo hacer montajes con la cara
of a youtuber as if it were being
de una youtube como si estuviera siendo
oral sex for the incredible clip that
sexo oral para el clip increíble que de
remembering everything you've done makes me
recordar todo lo que habéis hecho me da
tired man in the end nougat when
fatiga tío en final turrón que cuando a
kenia's accounts were closed this pair
kenia le cerraron las cuentas este par
of scoundrels took advantage of the moment
de sinvergüenzas aprovecharon el momento
to impersonate her they changed her
para suplantar su identidad le cambiaron
name the avatar and received the
el nombre el avatar y recibieron los
original videos of kenia pretending to be
vídeos originales de kenia haciéndose
kenia it's as if it were
pasa por kenia es como si fuera el canal
kenia's new channel okay with this they earned
nuevo de kenia vale con esto ganaron
almost half a million subscribers and
casi medio millón de suscriptores y
approximately three thousand dollars in photos
aproximadamente tres mil dólares en foto
see and we enter click and her name is kenia or that one
ver y entramos clic y se llama kenia o
and apparently she's a girl whose
ese y por lo visto es una chica a la
channel has been hacked therefore right
cual le han hackeado su canal por lo
now she doesn't have a channel and what has
tanto ahora mismo no tiene canal y qué
this little piece of [ __ ] done what does it
es lo que ha hecho el trocito de mierda
want it's a shame that's the shame that
este que quiere da pena eso es la pena
you  do this it's embarrassing come on and
que tú hagas esto da pena coge y se ha
the name of your channel has been changed the post
cambiado el nombre de su canal la puesto
and the banner of this youtuber is there and has
y el banner de la tal youtuber está y ha
uploaded a video called I'm
subido un vídeo que se llama ya estoy de
back
regreso
in the subscribers of this channel that they gave me
en los suscriptores de este canal que me
back the channel but I lost
regresaron el canal pero perdí
subscribers damn the
suscriptores coño que se ha perdido la
pay has been lost this one has like three million and
paga esta tiene como tres millones y
now has 100,000 subscribe to the million
ahora tiene 100.000 suscríbete al millón
I will do live not all of
haré en vivo no están aquí todos los
this girl's subscribers are here I already
suscriptores de esta chica ya te
missed you that we don't even love you come on
extrañaba que ni te amamos venga
calm down we will recover soon this
tranquila pronto nos recuperaremos eso
is a scam by all rules and they
en toda regla es una estafa y ellos lo
did it because they knew that she wanted to being
hicieron porque sabía que quería siendo
Mexican she was not going to get into
mexicana no se iba a meter en pleitos
legal disputes well when the truth
legales pues bien cuando ya la verdad
was Kenya created a channel again the
era kenia se volvió a crear un canal el
original they came out with peteneras
original ellos salieron por peteneras
saying that they are some friends of Kenya
diciendo que son unos amigos de kenia
who have formed another team to fight
que han formado otro team para luchar
against typhus kilos they mounted some
contra el tifus kilos se montaron unas
[ __ ] paranoia in their heads three lives
putas paranoias en la cabeza tres vidas
being an idea that
siendo tuve a una idea que hemos tenido
we have had and that we have not stolen the name
nosotros y que no la hemos robar nombre
from Kenya or
a kenia ni
anything it
ni nada
is an invention of ours the name
es una invención nuestra el nombre
at no time or has it been Kenya's idea
en ningún momento o ha sido idea de
although we  says the
kenia aunque nosotros dice los
wooden prisoners I'm not going to
prisioneros de madera no voy a
explain it but it seems like I wasn't looking at the
explicarlo pero como que no la miraba el
name to Kenya you piece of scoundrel to
nombre a kenia pedazo de sinvergüenza a
Kenya and to Kimberley okay because they have
kenia y a kimberley vale porque tienen
another secondary channel that is now where they
otro canal secundario que ahora es donde
upload their video clips that searching in the
suben sus videoclips que buscando en la
google cache we can see that
caché de google podemos ver que todavía
the photo of Kimberley still appears and the name
aparece la foto de kimberley y el nombre
of Kimberley okay at 800 thousand I will upload
de kimberley vale a los 800 mil subiré
episode 2 subscribe
el episodio 2 suscríbete
that they will continue working because it
que van a seguir trabajando porque ellos
is the only way they have to earn
es la única manera que tienen de ganar
money and that they have financial problems
dinero y que tienen problemas económicos
also that is the only way they
además que ellos la única forma que
have to earn money and they will continue
tienen de ganar dinero y van a seguir
working until someone does something
trabajando hasta que alguien haga algo
okay then he has run with his saint
vale entonces él ha corrido con su santo
with him and he tells me stop defaming this
con él y me dice deja de difamar este
channel it is not ours
canal no es nuestro
obviously this channel is
evidentemente evidentemente este canal
theirs okay I have proof of
si es de ellos vale tengo pruebas de
everything in the first place because I have all
todo en primer lugar porque tengo toda
the cache of that channel
la caché de ese canal
I am subscribed to that channel to
yo estoy suscrito a ese canal para
monitor it because I was monitoring it and
vigilarlo porque lo estuve vigilando y
that channel as I repeat to you has been
ese canal como os vuelvo a repetir se ha
called info I had it has been called its verse
llamado info tuve se ha llamado su verso
called kimberly loaiza it is called or  Kenya
llamado kimberly loaiza se llama o kenia
okay and also on the dog's channel on
vale y además en el canal del perro en
this channel that they are making now with
este canal que están haciendo ahora con
the dog's name they have had the
el nombre del perro han tenido encima la
shamelessness and the nerve to
poca vergüenza ya y la desfachatez de
put their original channel next to it in recommended channels,
poner al lado en canales recomendados su
well it is original that it is
canal original bueno es original que es
from Kenya that I am from them, they have
de kenia que de ellos estoy a ellos las
tried several times, okay, the fact of
intenta varias veces vale el hecho de
taking advantage of pretending to be the most
aprovechar hacerse pasar por youtube más
famous of them on YouTube to gain subscribers
famosos de ellos para ganar suscriptores
because they do not earn it themselves, okay,
porque por ellos mismos no lo ganan vale
but for you to say that they have not
pero que tú digas así que no lo han
stolen it in the name of Kenya when your channel,
robado en nombre kenia cuando tu canal
while it has even gained
mientras que hasta ha ganado
subscribers, it was because it had
suscriptores ha sido porque tenía puesto
the name Kenya OS and not only the
el nombre de kenia os y no sólo el
name, it is the name, the avatar
nombre es el nombre el avatar
and the videos, the monetized videos of
y los vídeos los vídeos monetizados de
them, shameless, you are a
ellas sin vergüenza que eres un
scoundrel, I mean, of all the
sinvergüenza o sea es que de todas las
[ __ ] that anyone in
cagadas que ha hecho cualquier de
October has done in the history of the internet, we already
octubre en la historia de internet ya
have them there or Cabrera with the
tenemos allá o cabrera con la puñalada
false stab in the back with those of the with those of
falsa arrese con los de los con los de
the cats with those of the bum, I think
los gatos con los del vagabundo yo creo
that the worst of the worst in these
que lo peor que lo peor en lo de esta
people but the worst and by far is
gente pero lo peor y con diferencias es
that you will never recover your
que ustedes jamás os vais a recuperar la
dignity, never scammers  we were I had
dignidad jamás estafadores estuvimos
it was born from an idea of ​​ours there is no there
tuve el nace de una idea nuestra no hay
is no reality there is no team that
no hay realidad no existe un team que
continues to put in I had to be from Kenya that
siga metiendo tuve que ser de kenia que
we stole it like many
nosotros lo hayamos robado como mucha
people are saying vocationally we wouldn't
gente está diciendo vocacional no
have this that we also have to
tendríamos esto que también tenemos que
thank you and tell you that thank you very much
agradecerlo y deciros que muchísimas
if for this well thanks are not
gracias si por esto bueno las gracias no
left by your fan it was known that you don't
se las deja tu fan se supo que tú no
have fans or for your work or anything like that
tienes fans ni a tu trabajo ni nada por
thanks for the plaque
el estilo las gracias de la placa
give it to you that it's worth it because they have
dársela que ya os vale porque se la han
stolen the plaque gives it to you or Kenya
robado la placa te la regala o kenia
I think it's great that you want to clarify
me parece genial que nos quiera aclarar
the fact that the whole show that they
el hecho de que todo el show que
put on as if Kenya was part of the
montaron como que kenia formaba parte de
shooting and the whole story was made up that
shooting y toda la historia hecha que
was false okay it seems to me your position face they
era falsa vale me parece tu puesto cara
want to recognize them but at no
los quieren reconocer pero en ningún
time telecom
momento telecom
the previous time the time when
la época anterior la época cuando
I received in the videos of Kenya
recibía en los vídeos de kenia
monetized and you were supplanting the
monetizado y estabais suplantando la
identity to such an extent to such an extent that they
identidad a tal punto a tal punto que
even took and manipulated stories of
hasta cogía y manipulaban historias de
this great from Kenya okay they cut
esta gran de kenia vale cortaban
words and edited them in such a way that it
palabras y las montaba de tal forma que
seemed that Kenya was saying
pareciera que estuviera kenia diciendo
that that channel was of their new type
que ese canal era de su nuevo tipo
us  we are an end we are a team and
nosotros somos un fin somos un equipo y
we support each other so I have to
nos apoyamos entre todos así que tengo
go support my teammates and well I
que ir a apoyar a mis compañeros y pues
have to say goodbye really
me tengo que despedir de verdad
thank you so much for being here
muchísimas gracias por estar aquí
too much too a video is coming there are
demasiado demasiado viene un vídeo hay
nerves I understand
nervios lo entiendo
as being subero I hope you are super
como estando subero espero estén súper
well and the badge to be verified
bien y lo de la placa ser verificado
now we are going to delve deeper into them
ahora vamos a profundizar más en ellos
because it is because these people at the
porque es porque esta gente en el
moment that Kenya opened her
momento que ya kenia se abrió su canal
real channel and they went with the roll that it
verdadero y ellos fueron con el rollo de
was conti and they began to create some
que era conti y empezaron a crear unos
videos a few strange not that they were already theirs they
vídeos un poco raritos no que ya eran de
already came out they no longer had
ellos ya salían ellos ya no tenían
views on the videos like a thousand views
visitas a los vídeos pues mil visitas
2,000 views 10,000 if anything with half a
2.000 visitas 10.000 si acaso con medio
million subscribers then they
millón de suscriptores entonces
started sending emails to YouTube
empezaron a mandarle email a youtube
complaining about why the videos did not
quejándose de porque los vídeos no
have views that surely there was a
tienen visitas que seguro que había una
black hand a paranoia that screw you or
mano negra una paranoia que te cagan o
because the videos now did not have views
que porque los vídeo ahora no tenían
that there was a black hand behind it
visita que había una mano negra detrás
why they did not give him the badge what
que porque no le daban la placa que
portions have verified and encourage with
porciones han verificado y animan con
this first hand on YouTube and I have
está de primera mano en youtube y tengo
the proof I have the proof if someone
las pruebas tengo las pruebas si alguien
comes to me and tells me that it is a lie without
me viene a decir que mentira sin
problem  I've done almost every night
problema hecho casi todas las noches
right and I have the proof of all of this
derecho y tengo las pruebas de todos
okay, these gentlemen were not going to give these gentlemen
vale estos señores no a estos señores no
the badge or the
le iban a dar ni la placa ni el
verification, they were not going to give it to them because
verificado no se la iba a dar porque en
YouTube knew they were scammers
youtube sabían que eran unos estafadores
what happens is that they couldn't close that channel
lo que pasa que ese canal no lo podían
unless it was that ña the one to
cerrar a no ser que fuera que ña la que
send YouTube to close that channel for
mandar a youtube a cerrar ese canal por
copyright not for
copyright no por suplantación de
identity theft and since Kenya was
identidad y como kenia estaba
with a thousand bigger worries than two
con mil preocupaciones mayores que dos
[ __ ] creeps attacking each other for two
putos rastrero de mierda se atacarán dos
thousand euros at her expense who was
mil euros a su costa quien estaba
having a very bad time at that moment well she didn't
pasándolo muy mal en ese momento no pues
have time to lose the two
no tenía tiempo para perder los dos
mongol the vouchers that in it she
mongol los vales que en ella se
spoke out after that now we go to that
pronunció después que ahora vamos a eso
but these two scoundrels YouTube
pero a estos dos sinvergüenzas youtube
had denied them the badge and the verification what
le tenía negada la placa y el verificado
happens is that when I said this in one of my
lo que pasa que cuando yo en uno de mis
live broadcasts I confirmed that YouTube did
directos dije esto confirme que youtube
not want to give them the badge and the verification they
no quería darle la placa y el verificado
went and contacted
cogieron y contactaron con el soporte de
YouTube support from another language from another country I don't
youtube de otro idioma de otro país no
know exactly which one okay I don't know if it can
sé exactamente cuál vale no sé si puede
be Russian or Arabic or some language very
ser ruso o árabe o algún idioma muy
far from Spanish they used the google
lejos del español usaron el google
translator and  They contacted them and
translator y contactaron con ellos y
tricked any mongol or
engañaron a cualquier mongol o del
support person who had no idea who
soporte que no tenía ni idea de quiénes
these two were, okay,
eran estos dos vale
that kid saw that he had more than 100
ese chaval pues vio que tenía más de 100
thousand subscribers and had already deleted all of
mil suscriptores ya tenía borrado todo
Kenya's content, okay, and then they
el contenido de kenia vale y entonces le
gave him the verifiable, they gave the badge if
dieron el verificable dieron la placa si
this is a lie what I'm saying
esto es mentira lo que estoy diciendo
Jesus or you know, you are invited to stop
jesús o sepas estáis invitados a pasar
by my live and show me how to
por mi directo y demostrarme lo
take advantage of
aprovecharnos
this, what happened that Kenya left team
esto qué pasó que kenia salió del team
week and that Kenya worked everything out,
week y que kenia elaboraron todo que a
who had already deleted the channel who
quien ya le borraron el canal que le
ordered her, the real ones grew, that great
ordenó las reales crecieron ese gran
point, they believed it, well, we were
punto lo creyeron pues nosotros fuimos
an opportunist and Guillermo, a
una oportunista y guillermo experimento
social experiment and nothing, finally we said,
social y nada para finalmente dijimos
let's use all the controversy that is being
vamos a utilizar toda la polémica que se
created with Kenya to do a
está creando con kenia para hacer un
social experiment and then return to the
experimento social y luego volver al
subject of the salsa singer, but things turned out
tema del salsero pero la cosa salió
quite well, much more than
bastante bien muchísimo más de lo que
we thought, a social experiment,
nosotros pensamos un experimento social
as I was telling you, this is a
como ya os iba diciendo esto es un puto
[ __ ] joke, a social experiment, it's not
cachondeo un experimento social no es
that, you piece of [ __ ], a
eso pedazo de sinvergüenza un
social experiment, it's a program with a
experimento social es un programa con
Mallorcan to Andalusia called
mallorquín a andalucía que se llama
wonderful people  where they put
gente maravillosa donde ponen en
people on the street in extreme situations
situaciones extremas a gente de la calle
for example a person messing with
por ejemplo una persona metiéndose con
a person from the GTV bus I don't
una persona del colectivo de gtv yo que
know a bill on the ground to see if
sé un billete en el suelo para ver si
someone picks it up someone's
alguien lo recoge que a alguien se le
wallet that is to say they give it back that
cala cartera es decir se la devuelve eso
is a social experiment what you have
es un experimento social lo que tú has
done is a scam okay scam because you
hecho una estafa vale estafa porque
are ignoring the time in which to
estás obviando el tiempo en el que
impersonate Kenya and it is
suplantar la identidad de kenia y está
simply explaining the time
explicando simplemente la época de
after the time when Kenya already had
después la época cuando ya kenia tenía
her original channel and you insist
su canal original y ustedes insisten
as you want friends of Kenya a show the
como queráis amigos de kenia un show el
hacker no no no don't
hacker no no no no
like them if it exists it's a [ __ ]
los guste de si existe es una puta
scam and if the thing like that went better
estafa y si la cosa así que salió mejor
than I expected and in fact earns six
de lo que esperaba y de hecho gana seis
thousand videos from subscribers and around
mil vídeos de suscriptores y alrededor
two thousand dollars a little more and
de unos dos mil dólares un poquito más y
we are going to meet for a video saying
vamos a quedar para un vídeo diciendo
all the mafia and the whole show that
toda la mafia y todo el show que montan
channels like Tadas Mes and Vargas put together and all
canales como tadas mes y vargas y todos
these types of channels and we are going to
estos tipos de canales y vamos a
dismantle it inside and continue with our
desmontarlo adentro y seguir con nuestro
channel of sal had surgery eye but as they
canal de sal se operó ojo pero como me
lower me in mount you piece of piece of
bajan en monta pedazo de pedazo de
[ __ ] piece of [ __ ] that you are a piece of
mierda pedazo de mierda que eres un
[ __ ] that you were going to dismantle
mierda que ibas a desmontar
where is where is the dismantled
dónde está dónde está lo desmontado
because I don't see it or rather everything that I
porque yo no lo veo o sea todo lo que yo
have told from the beginning until
he contado desde el principio hasta el
today I have the evidence here
día de hoy tengo las pruebas aquí
saved for the day that you have to have
guardadas para el día que tengas
balls that you will never have it
que tenga cojones que no lo vas a tener
and come to one of my live streams so that I can slam it
nunca y vengas a un directo mío a que te
in your mouth that but you will never
la dé en la boquita eso pero jamás vas a
have that one because he knows that it's all
tener esa pone porque sabe que todo es
true that's when I started to release the
verdad es cuando yo empecé a sacar las
evidence you wrote on youtube telling him
pruebas escribiste en youtube diciéndole
I am corrupt
soy unos corruptos
I am a mafia I am telling him
soy una mafia le estoy contando las
things about Javier Leira and he knows what the truth is he is
cosas de javier leira y sabe que verdad
spending on me and you know that it's true piece of
me gasta y sabes que es verdad pedazo de
[ __ ] that's why a
mierda por eso no va a aparecer un
live stream won't appear what is going to dismantle
directo que es lo que va a desmontar
Jesus and that you wrote info you see which
jesús y que escribías info tu ver que
was the name of your channel from the first
era el nombre de tu canal de primera
hour in the youtube search engine and it went
hora en el buscador de youtube y salía
to the studio channel with the name and the
al canal estudio con el nombre y el
avatar of Kenya Os and we went into your
avatar de kenia os y nos metemos en tu
channel and it was your channel and in fact then you
canal y era tu canal y de hecho luego lo
changed the name the handsome one being you
a cambio de nombre el apuesto siendo tú
see or rather everyone has seen with
ver o sea todo el mundo hemos visto con
our own eyes how you changed the
nuestros ojos cómo le cambiaste el
name of your channel you named it great and
nombre a tu canal le pusiste genial y
how  you had summarized in your channel and
como tenías resumido en tu canal y
monetized the videos of kenia or what are you going
monetizado los vídeos de kenia o que vas
to take down if we have all seen it with
a desmontar si todos lo hemos visto con
our eyes without shame that your
nuestros ojos sin vergüenza que se te
face should fall man that you are never
debería caer la cara tío que nunca jamás
going to erase this from your, from your
te vas a borrar esto de tu de tu
reputation you are never going to recover the
reputación jamás vas a recuperar la
dignity that what the
dignidad que eso de lo que están los
channels are like
canales
those that join together remain
ma los que se juntan entre ellos quedan
their little groups make pacts with youtube and they
sus grupitos hacen pactos con youtube y
think they are the mafia here this thing that
se creen que son aquí la mafia esto de
the channels join together to go
que los canales se juntan para ir en
against him is this straw that is made
contra de él está esta paja que se hace
of the [ __ ] head that is
de la puta cabeza que tiene la
important enough to form
importancia como para que se formen
cooperation groups against him
grupos de cooperación en contra de él
this already happened a year ago when he
esto ya lo hizo hace un año cuando
had a face to face debate with him and I
estuvo un debate cara a cara con él y lo
left him on the floor okay and he also said
deje por los suelos vale y también decía
that we were a mafia against
que es que éramos una mafia en contra de
him okay what we were debating
él vale lo que le estábamos debatiendo
was the fact that he had
era el hecho de que había de que había
made a video with a thumbnail with the
hecho un vídeo con una miniatura con la
photo of mieres like photoshopped like he
foto de mieres como photoshopeada como
was eating a [ __ ] okay and
que se estaba comiendo una polla vale y
all of us who were in that debate
todos los que estábamos en ese debate
were against that for
estábamos en contra de eso por razones
obvious reasons for obvious reasons and this
obvias por razones evidentes y éste
mongolo said that nobody supported me
mongolo decía que nadie me apoyaba
because we were all friends you have
porque todo éramos amigos tú tienes
direct contact with dallas or have you
contacto directo con dallas o has tenido
ever had contact with the accountants if I
alguna vez contacto de los contadores si
don't have and the 10
no tengo y los 10
the section has to be a pain in the ass
el apartado tiene que ser un pesado de
three pairs of balls depending on what's wrong with
tres pares de cojones según qué pasa
you
contigo
if I slept at his house like at his house
si yo dormí en su casa como en su casa
at my friend's not what he's defending
en mi amiga no lo que está defendiendo
sucking up support for a guy you don't
chupando el apoyo a un tío que no lo
know at all the mother because there was
conoces de nada la madre porque estaba
a bomb retweet
un retweet bomba
then don't get into
entonces no te metas en terreno
swampy ground asleep with her
pantanoso dormido con ella
the beginning house you who have to walk
el comienzo casa tú que tienes que andar
the one who is where you and who is putting
la que está donde tú y que está puesto
a comment on the video the fia who
un comentario en el vídeo la fia que
is in first marking and another of your
está en primero marcando y otra de tu
face ca
cara
n't find me because he has 700 thousand
no me encuentra porque tiene 700 mil
subscribers
suscriptores
jesus one thing dallas has ever
jesús una cosa dallas alguna vez ha
said makes this video like this like that and I've already
dicho hace este vídeo así asá y esto ya
said this before that no that I pay him maybe
lo he dicho antes que no que yo le pagas
I some video and I told him you
a lo mejor yo algún vídeo y le dije tú
just get the little things out of you don't legacy have
sólo te saca las cositas no lega haber
delayed don't do little things to yourself god
retrasado no te hagas cositas dios
recently of workers that I don't see what was
hace poco de trabajadoras que no vea lo
cured the videos eggs the
que se curaba los videos huevos los
books and the edition  of the envious videos
libros y la edición de los vídeos
a person
una persona
does whatever it takes to get views they do
hace lo que sea para ganar visitas lo
whatever it takes it's a thumbnail of a
hace lo que sea es una miniatura de una
[ __ ] eating a girl and they are in
polla comiéndole a una chavala y que
charge of YouTube that they can do whatever they
mandan en youtube que pueden hacer lo
want and for whoever they want but not to
que quieran y para quien quiera pero no
prove that it's impossible that here nobody no matter
demostrar eso impossible que aquí nadie
how many numbers someone has than
por mucho más números que tenga de
someone no matter how much
alguien que alguien por mucho menos que
less contact they have they don't go to who
más contacto que tengan no van a quien
anyone on YouTube and that's why we for
nadie de youtube y por eso nosotros por
all this because I was on this
todo esto porque estuve en este canal
verified channel and we have our right
verificado y tenemos nuestro derecho de
because you have the badge and the
porque tenéis la placa y el canal
verified channel I just explained it I know a few
verificado lo acabo de explicar sé unos
minutes if for whatever reason you think you
minutos si por algo que sea creéis que
can prove that something I've
podéis demostrar que algo de lo que
said is a lie you have the doors
dicho es mentira tenéis las puertas
open to come debate it with me
abiertas para venir a debatirlo conmigo
live whenever you want what happens is that it
en directo cuando queráis lo que pasa es
's impossible because you know that
que es imposible porque que sabéis que
everything I'm saying is true and that
todo lo que estoy diciendo es verdad y
someone wants to stop us and it's
eso de que alguien nos quiere parar y es
impossible if it stops it's totally
imposible si se para es totalmente
impossible it's impossible to stop you're worth it
imposible es imposible frenar os vale
because you're already going downhill you see
porque ya vais cuesta abajo ya veis
downhill or so I remember that
cuesta abajo o sea me acuerdo que hace
recently I have a video on my channel
poco tengo un vídeo en mi canal
commenting on a fake raffle that exists in which it is
comentando un sorteo falso que existe en
supposed that  500,000
el que se supone que a los 500.000
subscribers and you're going to raffle off a couple of
suscriptores y vais a sortear un par de
iPhones, okay, better change the
iphone vale más vale que cambien las
rules of the contest and the raffles at
normas del concurso y los sorteos a los
400,000 because you're already closer
400.000 porque ya los tenéis más cerca
than the 500,000 ones, okay, because you're
que los de los 500.000 vale porque es
going downhill without brakes, nobody
que vais cuesta abajo y sin freno nadie
has to pay because you're going backwards
tiene que pagar porque vais para atrás
anyway, she has
de todas forma
always been on the right track,
tenía siempre ha estado desde el punto
from the minute she has been informed of
desde el minuto se ha estado informa de
all the positions, in contact with her,
todos los puestos en contacto con ella
we have not contacted people
no hemos puesto contacto con gente de su
around her and she knew all this but she
entorno y ella sabía todo esto pero ella
has never spoken about this that Kenya has never
nunca ha hablado de esto que kenia nunca
spoken about in fact but since you have the
ha hablado de hecho pero como tienen la
toughest nerve
cara más dura
Kenya made a story on Instagram
kenia hizo una historia en instagram
complaining about you guys saying that you were
quejándose de ustedes diciendo que erais
[ __ ] workers who had been
unos putos trabajadores que habían
scamming your subscribers
estado estafando a sus suscriptores
by impersonating them and then you
suplantando su identidad y que después
started telling the story that she was
empezaste a decir la historia de que era
part of your team and yet it still works and those
parte de vuestro team y aún así consiste
Instagram stories and they
y esas historias instagram y las
modify them to use it in your favor what a
modifican para usarlo a vuestro favor
[ __ ] scoundrel am I what a
que puto sinvergüenza soy yo
[ __ ] if it's not, no, it can't be, she
que puta si es que no no no puede ser
wanted to touch on this subject because she
había querido tocar este tema porque
simply wants to ignore it but I think
simplemente lo quiere ignorar pero creo
that is already necessary there is a channel that is
que ya es necesario hay un canal que es
completely false called team 2 I
completamente falso que se llama team 2
had something like that when they deleted my
tuve algo así cuando a mí me eliminaron
channel they started to summarize all
el canal ellos empezaron a resumir todos
my videos then they started to
mis vídeos entonces ellos empezaron a
accumulate a lot of subscribers
acumular muchísimos suscriptores
now when I opened my new channel
ahora cuando yo abrí mi nuevo canal
they started to give explanations
ellos empezaron a dar explicaciones
saying that I had contacted them and
diciendo que yo los había contactado y
that I was supporting them and things like that
que yo los estaba apoyando y cosas así
all the information that comes from that
toda la información que venga de ese
channel that ninis is completely false I have
canal que ninis es completamente falsa
never contacted them apart from that they are
nunca los he contactado aparte que están
saying that the supposed hacker who
diciendo que el supuesto hacker que me
deleted my channel is contacting
eliminó mi canal los está contactando a
them being that I am not a victim of
ellos siendo que yo no soy víctima de
any hacker I was not bothered by the fact
ningún hacker no me molestaba el hecho
that they were summarizing my videos
de que estuvieran resumiendo mis vídeos
and earning money from them because they are
y ganar dinero de ellos porque los están
monetizing them does not bother me at all
monetizando no me molesta en lo absoluto
but saying this type of things and
pero ya diciendo este tipo de cosas y de
lies and the worst thing is that you
mentiras y lo peor que ustedes se las
believe them that does bother me too much and I am not
crean eso sí me molesta demasiado y no
going to allow it and we are going to the
lo voy a permitir y vamos a el
social experiment as I have said
experimento social como he dicho
equality with a future but all the magic
igualdad con futuro pero toda la magia
that these channels have set up and seeing
que tiene montada estos canales y ver
that this exploded we say come on let's take
que esto explotó decimos vamos vamos a
advantage of this and let's create a
aprovechar esto y vamos a crear ya un
channel in which we can create our
canal en el que podamos crear nuestro
own content and take out whatever we want
propio contenido y sacar lo que nosotros
own content they
nos dé la gana su propio contenido
just said
acaban de decir
[Music]
[Música]
and that we saw that the public reaction
y que vimos que la reacción del público
was very very pretty good for people
era muy muy bastante buena para la gente
were liking our videos
le estaba gustando nuestros vídeos
on the channels these sayings of criticism
por los canales estos dichos de críticas
that are gathered between them are all
que se juntan entre ellos son todos
friends and yes well one thing and tremendous and
amigos y si bueno una cosa y tremenda y
the thing was that many influenced
la cosa fue que muchas influenciadas
this load of the opportunist
esta carga de la oportunista
took advantage of this to decide many
aprovecharon esto para decidir muchas
barbarities and lies and people with
barbaridades y mentiras y la gente con
many people believed it and they called us
mucha gente lo creyó y nos decían
scammers that I don't know what you don't do how
estafadores que no sé qué no hacéis
many
cuantos
tell me please that I did not just hear
dime por favor que no acabo de escuchar
that I was called an opportunist by a guy who
que me ha llamado oportunista un tío que
took advantage of the misfortune and the evil that
aprovecho la desgracia y el mal que pasó
a girl who lost her channel with 3
una chiquilla que perdió su canal con 3
million subscribers went through to
millones suscriptores para suplantar la
impersonate her and profit from it like
identidad y lucrarse de ello como que
channels that were based on four
canales que se basaban en cuatro
lies and four nonsense to
mentiras y en cuatro tonterías para
throw [ __ ] at you call you a scammer Jesus
echarte mierda llamarte estafador jesús
I was based on the fact that I searched for the name of your
me basaba en que buscaba el nombre de tu
channel on YouTube and a channel
canal en youtube y aparecía un canal
called Kenya 2 appeared where
llamado kenia 2 donde estaban resumidos
all of their videos were summarized and monetized I was based on the fact
todos sus vídeos y monetizados me basaba
that you were then bragging and
en que luego estuviste alardeando y
hesitating beating your chest
vacilando dándote golpe en el pecho
super proud of having earned about
súper orgulloso de haber ganado unos
three or four thousand dollars at the expense of
tres mil o cuatro mil dólares a costa de
the scam I was basing it on the fact that I have some
la estafa me basaba en que tengo unos
private messages that you had with
mensajes privados que tú has tenido con
Dallas acknowledging that you did this scam
dallas reconociendo que esta estafa la
taking advantage of the fact that a
has hecho aprovechando que una youtuber
Mexican youtuber and that she is not going to report you
mexicana y que no te va a denunciar
because if it had been a
porque si hubiera sido una youtuber
Spanish youtuber she wouldn't have done it I'll tell you
española no lo hubiera hecho te digo en
what else I was basing it on Jesus eats the eggs
que más me basaba jesús come los huevos
pieces of [ __ ] it's a very brutal
trozos de mierda es una forma muy bestia
and disgusting way well yes no
y asquerosa pues sí no
but my current financial situation is not such that I can
pero mi situación económica actual no
continue uploading videos to
está para seguir subiendo vídeos a
youtube and earn ten euros every so many
youtube y gana diez euros cada equis
months you did it because I needed
meses tú lo ha hecho porque necesitaba
money because you're a starving man and you
pasta porque eres un muerto de hambre y
don't have the balls to make a living with
no tienes cojones a buscarte la vida con
your own hands with your own work and you
tus manos con tus manos con tu trabajo y
've had it almost illegally about the
lo has tenido casi ilegalmente lo del
channel yes it's true that you can
canal sí es cierto que me lo puedes
delete it at any time you
borrar en cualquier momento denunciarme
could also report me but I doubt I would want to more
también podría pero dudo que quiera más
than anything because of the country where it is if it were
que nada por el país donde es si fuese
Spain logically I wouldn't have done it I
españa lógicamente no lo había hecho o
mean without shame that you are admitting
sea sin vergüenza que estás reconociendo
in this [ __ ] conversation with all your
en esta puta conversación por toda la
face that you are doing it taking advantage of the fact
cara que lo estás haciendo aprovechando
that the girls from another  country that if it were
que las chicas de otro país que si fuera
in Spain I wouldn't do it you're a
en españa no lo haría eres un
wretch from the south you're a wretch I'm
desgraciado del sur eres un desgraciado
going to repeat this for all these
voy a repetir esto para todos estos
channels that I'm the scammers I don't
canales que soy yo los estafadores ni
even know what on YouTube we wouldn't have
siquiera sé lo que en youtube ni
this that I'm bringing out again nor would we
tendríamos esto que lo vuelvo a sacar ni
have the channel verified so
tendríamos el canal verificado así que
if you read that for that reason these values ​​or
si usted ley que por eso estos valores o
the videos that are these values
los vídeos que son estos valores
the answer is look at YouTube no to all
la respuesta es mira youtube no a todo
this YouTube knows how things
esto de youtube sabe sabe las cosas como
are and those who have responded are YouTube there is
son y los que han respondido son youtube
no or does not send from YouTube YouTube
no hay o no manda desde youtube youtube
of course I don't send on YouTube
por supuesto que yo no mando en youtube
okay of course I'm nobody on
vale yo por supuesto no soy nadie en
YouTube it's simply I know some
youtube es simplemente conozco algunas
people who give me information
personas que me pasan informaciones
follow 22 what I'm saying I've already
siguen 22 lo que estoy diciendo ya se lo
told you like three or four times in
he dicho como tres o cuatro veces en
this video but I'll repeat it again if
este vídeo pero lo vuelvo a repetir si
anything I say is a lie come and
es mentira algo de lo que digo venir y
tell me to my face come come but with your
decírmelo a la cara venid venid pero con
face uncovered you sons of [ __ ] YouTube
la cara destapada hijos de puta youtube
knows perfectly well who it is today and
sabe perfectamente quién es hoy y por
that's why you had to contact the YouTube
eso tuviste que contactar con el youtube
of another language I would love to have
de otro idioma que me encantaría haber
seen your interaction with the
visto la interacción de ustedes con el
YouTube of another language when  either it is
youtube de otro idioma cuando ya sea se
understood very little in Spanish I would
entiende bastante poco en español
love YouTube they tell you I have
me encantaría youtube te dicen tengo
contacts within YouTube
contacto dentro de youtube
not to stay that it relieves anything the
que no se quede que releva nada la
verification that they are not going to give you the
verificación que no le van a dar la
plate the lie they have nothing they are
placa la mentira no tienen nada son
people if not we would not have this
gente si no no tendríamos esto
nobody is going to stop us the goddess for
nadie nos va a parar la de la diosa para
Jesus let's take a look at your
jesús vamos a echa un vistazo a vuestros
social networks but I [ __ ] on this
sociables pero me cago en la puta esto
what the [ __ ] have I done a massacre if this
qué coño he hecho una masacre si esto
is brown what do you tell me about the bank or that
está marrón que me cuenta del banco o
machu that nobody goes to
sea aquella machu que nadie va para el
Jesus that nobody is going to stop you from falling
jesús a que nadie os va a parar de caer
not because I am on my period or even if I
no porque estoy a la regla ni aunque
do a collaboration with Vegeta this is
haga una colaboración con vegeta esto ya
no longer fixable that channel will not be
no tiene arreglo ese canal no lo
resurrected not even the Bible look at how they are [ __ ]
resucita ni la biblia fíjate si son
crawlers and disgusting rats
rastreros de mierda y ratas asquerosas
that right now after everything they have
que ahora mismo después de todo lo que
done what I think is very good that
han hecho lo que me parece muy bien que
in part they apologize to the audience
en parte pidan disculpas a la audiencia
for what they have done but they need to
por lo que han hecho pero les falta
return the money they have stolen from
devolver el dinero que le han robado a
Kenya and they need to recognize that what
kenia y les falta reconocer que lo que
they have done is a scam because at
han hecho es una estafa porque es que en
no time do they mention the above the
ningún momento mencionan lo anterior lo
above of creating be  red tuber and
anterior de crear ser tintos tuber y
all this [ __ ], not
toda la mierda de esta no la
identity theft, Jesus, that's
suplantación de identidad jesús eso es
what you have to recognize and give
lo que tienes que reconocer y devolverle
Kenya her money back. But look,
el dinerito a la kenya pero fíjate si
they are so creepy, they've been doing that fiction for a while,
son rastrero que durante un tiempo han
which
estado haciendo esa esa ficción lo que
in the end is okay, it doesn't
al fin y al cabo bueno vale a mí no me
seem like the channels that make fiction anymore,
parece más los canales que hacen ficción
not like they call me Freddy, help
no como me llaman freddy auxilio
Android. The event, which may be very
android el evento que puede ser muy
ridiculous, may be very pathetic, but in the
ridículo puede ser muy patético pero al
end, well, it's a spectacle
fin y al cabo pues bueno es espectáculo
here. What I find
aquí lo que me parece de una poca
incredibly shameless is the
vergüenza increíble es la suplantación
identity theft and obvious things and other things. I don't
de identidad y obvias y otras cosas no
know if I'm wrong, but I think that
sé si me equivocaré pero yo creo que la
Jesus is not the one leading this. I
batuta de esto no la lleva de jesús yo
think he knows,
creo que el sepas
even though he's a little lacking in lights and
aunque les falte un poquito de luces y
such, if it weren't for the fact that he has this
tal si no fuera porque tiene al lado a
piece of rabble next to him, this piece of
este pedazo de gentuza a este pedazo de
scoundrel, he would be a better person. I don't know
sinvergüenza sería mejor persona no sé
if I'm wrong, they both have the same
si me equivoco los dos tienen la misma
responsibility because even though the channel
responsabilidad porque aunque el canal
is Jesus's, he knows he's showing his face
sea de jesús el sepa está dando la cara
and is supporting him. But I don't know if I'm
y lo está acompañando pero no sé si me
wrong, but it gives me the same.  the impression
equivoco pero a mí me da la impresión de
that if I didn't have these
que si no tuviera al lado a estas
vermin, this disgusting rat, maybe I
sabandijas a esta rata asquerosa quizás
could be a better person and as I was
podría ser mejor persona y como iba
saying, look at everything they've
diciendo fijaros en todo lo que han
done, everything that has harmed
hecho en todo lo que ha perjudicado a
Kenya, imagine for a moment being in
kenia imaginaros por un momento estar en
Kenya's period with how bad it's been
el periodo de kenia con lo mal que lo ha
through and having to put up with this
pasado y tener que aguantar está
sclerosis, okay, imagine now
esclerosi that vale imaginaros que ahora
that I can't count on that, now after
que no contar con eso ahora después de
all Kenya's followers have won, they've
que han ganado todos los seguidores de
been pretending that they have a
kenia han estado fingiendo que tienen un
team with Kenya, that they are with Kenya, now
team con kenia que están con kenia ahora
in the controversy of book and against Kenya,
en la polémica de book y lo contra kenia
as they are more interested in Juan de Dios'
como les interesa más juan de dios'
Pantoja, who have more subscribers and
pantoja que tienen más suscriptores y
have more fans who are going to support them, they have
tienen más fans que los van a apoyar han
made a series of videos throwing
hecho una serie de vídeos tirándole
[ __ ] at Kenya and supporting Juan de Dios'
mierda kenia y apoyando a juan de dios'
Pantoja, this is what these rats do,
pantoja esto es lo que hacen estas ratas
okay, I have compared many times the
vale yo he comparado muchas veces el
sanse or Kenya and the same as God in
sanse o de kenia y de igual de dios en
Mexico as in Spain, the one in Dallas,
méxico como en españa el de dallas
linear, well when the one in Spain was happening,
lineales pues cuando pasaba el de españa
Dallas and Mares,
de dallas y mares
this is  this rat this disgusting rat
esto es esta rata esta rata asquerosa
was sucking the whole penis but like this
estaba chupando de todo el pene pero así
raising and lowering the foreskin burns it
levantando y bajando el prepucio arda la
but in a way that endorses them and you're
pero de una forma que los avale y lo
going to see it in the videos with bojan in the
vais a ver en los vídeos con bojan en la
description because dallas was the one with the most
descripción porque dallas era el que más
subscribers and the one who was most
suscriptores tenía y el que más
interested in supporting and the easiest to
interesaba apoyar y el más fácil para
win I don't know to try to stay the
ganar yo que sé para intentar quedar la
law of tui or something you are really disgusting
ley de tui o algo dais mucho asco
jesulín future after this video they
jesulín future después de este vídeo
also sent me a series of tweets
también me lanzaron una serie de tweets
we were arguing on twitter and I
estuvimos discutiendo en twitter y yo le
responded to that in a live that I have
he respondido a eso en un directo que lo
summarized in the secondary channel I'm
tengo resumió en el canal secundario lo
going to leave the description too and
voy a dejar también la descripción y
you can see how he passed his penis through his
podéis verlo como le pasó el pene por la
mouth jesus beats him up
boca jesús le mete una paliza por
unfortunately I would like to give it to you live in a
desgracia me gustaría dártela en un
face to face live
directo en un cara a cara en directo
but that's not going to happen that is a
pero eso no va a pasar eso es una
fantasy that is not going to happen because you will never
fantasía que no va a pasar porque jamás
have the balls because it is
vas a tener cojones porque es que
absurd it would be suicide knowing that
absurdo sería un suicidio sabiendo que
I have everything I have said in evidence
tengo todo lo que he dicho en pruebas
without further ado gentlemen subscribe if you don't
sin más señores suscribiros si no me
know me and I hope that  I hope you liked
conocéis y espero que os haya gustado
this video a lot, see you in the
mucho este vídeo nos vemos en el
next one.
siguiente